(Rodtang) Does Fuse have his happiness?
(Nai) She's freaking pretty.
(Rodtang) I thought it's Tee.
(Nai) Huh?
(Rodtang) Didn't you see?
(Rodtang) Tee acted like a gatekeeper.
(Rodtang) I couldn't even get near Fuse.
(Fuse) It's starting to be unfair to her.
(Lookmo) I do understand that she's
done something unfair to you first.
(Lookmo) But you shouldn't have done it like her.
(Lookmo) Being two-timing isn't cool at all.
I think...
I'll break up with her.
Are you following me?
Well, we're heading the same way.
I'm taking BTS too.
We live in the same alley.
If you don't believe me,
I'll show you my keycard.
Goodbye, guys. That's all for today. I'm leaving.
Oh no!
What is your dog's name?
Locky.
Whoa, Locky is way cuter than you.
Hey.
Ouch.
Mhek've kept the keycard for you.
Just get it back tomorrow.
You can sleep here tonight.
Thank you.
What about your parents?
They're not home.
You know what, you live right near my condo.
I'll come over to your place often then.
If you foget your keycard again,
I let you sleep there.
At the bus stop.
You act so tough.
But a real tough guy...
wouldn't have taken me home.
Locky.
Come here.
Why did you become the head of the cheer club?
I enjoy doing activities.
But it's so tired.
Yeah, but we're in it together.
We share the same goal.
We are united.
I think certain things...
belong only in our high school years.
I'm afraid I might regret not doing it.
You're so cool.
Will you bring your happiness to the event?
You mean my partner?
I'm single.
Even Fuse is taken.
How can someone as cool as you be single?
Well...
I don't know. I wish I had one.
Do you want to be in a relationship?
I do.
But I don't have time to pursue a relationship.
Don't do anything. Just let me pursue you.
Can I pursue you, the head of cheer club?
(Four days before the friendly match)
(Three days before the friendly match)
Perfect.
Whoo!
Rodtang.
Teach him properly.
What's up, bro?
We need to talk. Now.
Go.
Mhek.
Don't you think Nai
is acting a bit weird around Rodtang?
I thought it was just me. I'll look into it.
Um.
I think I'll break up with her.
(Are you free this evening?)
(Nope, I have a tutoring class.)
(Do you have a minute? A quick call is fine.)
(Wait a sec, I'll take a shower first.)
(Are you done with your shower?)
(LOL. Wait a sec, I'm with my mom now.)
When will I get to tell her?
Fuse.
How's it going?
My assisstant drum major.
Can to teach me twirling?
I want to be good at twirling.
Twirling?
-Show him.
-Like this?
Hey, not like that.
Like this.
Enough.
Sit down.
Being handsome is tough.
You have to be a drum major.
Look at ordinary people like us.
Living the easy life.
Yeah, I can get plenty of sleep...
and poop in peace.
That's smelly.
You got this.
I'll sleep enough for both of us.
Let me go!
CPA, keep going! CPA, keep going!
Can I lie down here?
What?
Hey.
Go get your work done. Get up.
Go get your work done.
Nah.
Hey.
I thought ordinary people
were supposed to get plenty of sleep,
and poop in peace.
What are we doing here?
Thanks for your help.
I'm shorthanded. I wouldn't
have made it without you all.
Ugh.
I can't do it this anymore. I need a break.
Here.
I bought snacks for you guys.
If you get it dome before 10 pm,
I'll treat you to pizza.
Hey.
Guys.
Boost your energy.
Let's get it done.
Hurry up.
Hey, how come you got most of them?
Yeah, why did you get the most?
Being handsome has its perks.
Fuse.
Hey.
Thanks.
Why Fuse can have it before 10 pm?
Yeah, is that a benefit of beauty privillege?
So unfair. I'm a bit upset.
Uh.
The bathroom is vacant now.
Who's gonna take a shower?
Me.
Me first.
Wait for me.
Do you need any help?
I'm good.
I want to help you.
You want to help me?
Um.
Go ahead then.
I was just about to be lazy.
Come lie down here.
My ass.
Tee.
You want some?
I'm hard to get.
Well, I love difficult things.
Tee, my finger.
What are you doing?
Tee.
Tee, are you free?
Is this the right one?
Yeah.
Thanks for coming with me.
You really didn't have to come with me.
You already showered.
Why did you come?
I just want to come here with you.
Don't leave yet.
Let's grab some desserts.
Champ will nag us.
Ugh.
Forget him.
Let's grab some desserts.
Please?
Well, let's go to a place nearby.
Okay.
How about Mhek's shop?
Cool.
Just tell him.
Watch your step.
(One day before the friendly match)
(D-day of the friendly match.)
I think that's enough.
You've taken so many pictures with him.
Tee, you're amazing.
In the last pic, you basically his watermark.
That's great.
I want to be his watermark in every pictures.
Are you here to upstage me?
Stay still, let me wipe your sweat.
Aren't you a bit too handsome today?
I think I'm handsome every day.
Keep it.
For wiping your sweat.
Thank you.
Why are you smiling?
Nothing.
Have you eaten yet?
Right, I haven't eaten yet.
You won't have energy for it later.
I was waiting for you.
Let's grab something to eat then.
May I borrow him for a minute?
Where are you two going?
Going out.
Going out?
Going to grab a meal.
Well, enjoy your meal.
Of course he'll enjoy it, right?
Tee.
I mean a meal.
You're messing with me now.
Ugh.
Whoa.
Do you think I'm eating too much?
That's good. You'll need a lot of energy today.
But my pants are too tight now.
Is that all you eat?
Seeing you enjoy your food makes me happy.
Why?
About yesterday...
Ah.
Abou that matter.
Are you okay?
Let me know if you need anything.
Honestly, it's not like I'm not okay.
I just don't understand...
why she lied to me.
I think after this event,
I'm going to have a serious talk with her.
Hey.
Nai called a meeting.
I'm looking forward to
seeing the assistant drum major.
Wait and watch me too.
Watch you?
Let's go.
Change it.
Okay, okay.
Move it down a bit.
This one, Mhek.
It's pretty good.
Go get a table.
Okay.
Move it up a bit.
Hey.
Isn't it heavy? Can I give you a hand?
Leave me alone.
Ouch.
You could've just said you like it rough.
We need some music for this.
Three, two, go.
FrameBook is cute, lovely in the court.
FrameBook is playful, and so cute when they play.
FrameBook is cute.
Louder, louder.
Lovely in the court. FrameBook is playful.
And so cute when they play.
Hey, who's cute? Me?
Not you, man. Not you.
Am I not cute?
From this moment forward,
I'm Teacher Molly.
(Teacher Molly)
I am delighted to welcome all of you...
who gather in this institution.
The prestigious institution.
I hope eveyone is having a joyful day today.
On behalf of all the teachers, I declare the event...
officially starts now.
Here!
Let's start!
Fuse.
That's Fuse.
Front twirl, one set. Ready, set.
Let's get it, Fuse.
Here.
I accidently bought extra.
So here you go.
It's an extra one.
Thanks.
You can drink it.
Why don't you sit with your friends?
I want to sit here.
Can I sit here?
Hey.
You killed it.
Nailed it.
I should probably ask for
your autrograph in advance.
Me too. Me too.
Our school drum majors are really cool today.
Yeah.
By the way, where is Rodtang?
Right, he told me he's going to a bathroom.
Ah.
Fuse, I took so many pictures of you.
Turn on your AirDrop.
Really?
Um.
I don't have my phone with me right now.
What?
Where did you leave it?
I don't know.
It's fine.
I guess I might be lost by now.
I'll send them to you later then.
Well, where is Tee?
Hey, that's Tee.
Are you a basketball player?
A substitute.
I'm probably play in the second half.
By coming to this room...
Are you looking for something in here?
I'm here to get some encouragement.
Well, go get them. I'm screaming for you.
Hey, not you.
It's him. Sit down.
Sit down.
Can I have some encouragement?
Oh, what is this?
I just dropped my thing. Can you pick it up for me?
You got this.
I wish you a victory and stay safe.
I'm rooting for you.
I feel encouraged now.
I have to go.
Um.
You got this.
Wish you stay safe, baby.
I...
I officially declare the 2026 annual
friendly basketball match to start now.
Why don't you belive me?
That you like me?
I'm telling the truth. I'm swear to my life.
Your oath means nothing.
You were messing with me few days ago.
Then you're telling me that you like me now?
Isn't it too fast?
Why does it have to be slow?
I've already thought about it.
I've liked you since the day you helped me.
What would you do if I weren't here?
I'm sorry.
On that day, you were hurt because of me.
But you didn't say a word to blame me.
You even allowed me to sleep at your place.
You know what?
When you were playing with Locky,
you're freaking cute.
It made me want to be a dog.
Just so you might like me.
Because I really like you.
Are you crazy?
You want to be a dog?
I actually don't want to be a dog.
I want to be your happiness.
You're smiling.
That means you're happy, right?
That's nonsense.
If you're not ready for a relationship,
we can just be in a talking stage for now.
Just give me a chance.
I don't do the talking stage.
Let's just date.
If it doesn't work out, we can break up.
Deal?
Really?
But I can't guarantee it.
You might break up with me tomorrow.
I'm serious.
-Um.
-We won't break up.
Let's just make it through tomorrow.
Nai.
Hey, someone might see us.
My happiness.
Let's go.
It has to be NaiRodtang.
Hello.
I have a question. If I were a superhero,
which superhero would I be?
Superman?
Nope.
Batman?
Spider-Man?
Nope.
The answer is...
Your-Man!
Isn't it funny?
Here, have some water to cool down.
I'm good. Is he crazy?
Fine, I'll drink it by myself.
What?
Over there!
Thank you for helping me.
I don't know what I would've done without you.
Don't mention it.
I'm also struggling with it.
By the way, are we friends now?
Is it you who keep liking my posts?
We're friends now. I gotta go.
You got this, Tee.
You got this.
Go get them, Tee.
Go get them.
Hey, Sys.
Hey, you're so cool in this morning.
(Sys)
I already tagged you in the photo.
Really?
I'll check it later.
Hey, look.
Tee is pretty handsome.
Yeah, he is.
But he's a bit show-off.
Do you know if he's seeing someone?
Are you asking me?
You seems pretty close to him.
I don't know.
Why did you ask?
Fuse!
Rodtang!
I've been looking for you.
I thought you had already gone home.
You're busy doing...
Nothing.
Right, I've met your girlfriend
in front of the gymnasium.
Huh?
Gosh.
I have to go.
Block him.
Yeah, keep going.
Go, go.
What's wrong?
Don't follow me.
Hey, where are you now?
I'm in front of the building.
Have you been waiting for a while?
Not at all.
I've just arrived.
What about you?
I've arrived for a while.
It's been a while.
Shall we get inside?
Jeen.
Fuse.
What a coincidence.
It's Lakers team, damn.
It's not... it's not that intense.
Not intense.
It's easy like playing for fun.
Maybe...
You haven't met him before, have you?
This is mine. Yours is...
This one.
Try it.
Shall we buy neckties?
That's Tea, my brother.
What's going on between Fuse and you?
That's not how friends treat each other.
Aren't you happy Jeen doesn't have anyone else?
You can't control...
who you fall in love with or when it happens.
It's more about...
how you handle it.
I think we should take a break.
I need some time to think.